rssmountain.com 2012-06-11

# RSSMountain - Privacy and Security

**  
Your Privacy**

RSSMountain.COM®, recognizes and respects the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers, registered members ("Members") and users, and has established this Privacy Policy as a result. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of:

• the personal information we may collect from you when you visit our web site, respond to our emails  
• why we gather information from you,  
• how we collect it,  
• how we use it, and  
• the choices you have regarding our use of personal information you have provided.

This Privacy Policy is part of the Terms of Use, which governs your use of our web site located at www.RSSMountain.COM® or the "Web Site"). The Web Site is owned by RSSMountain.com, Inc. (the "Company"). 

_Note: You must be 18 years or older to use, subscribe or register as a member of RSSMountain.COM®. The Web Site is a general audience site and we do not knowingly collect, maintain or disclose personal information from or about children.  
_  
**Why do we gather information?  
**  
RSSMountain.COM® gathers personal information to help improve our products and customer service, to communicate with you, to process your orders, to provide an enhanced and more personalized experience and to inform you of special offers and services from us.

**What information do we gather?  
**  
First name, last name, email address and your website address.

**How we use the information we collect?  
**  
We use information we collect to communicate with you, to process your orders, to provide an enhanced and more personalized experience, and to inform you. Under no circumstances, we sell or make available to others your personal information.

|   
---|---
